{
    "id": "62953e51a40c4464b1f6dc5fb1a16b15",
    "title": "General Grammar And Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There are some beautiful ………………………… trees in the garden.",
            "description": "We use tall for people, buildings, trees etc.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "high",
                "long"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The prison has got very ………………………. walls.",
            "description": "Generally speaking, tall is used for things that are higher than they are wide. High is used in other cases.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "high",
                "long"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the ………………………………. mountain in the world?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "highest",
                "tallest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That building is about 300 feet ……………………………..",
            "description": "In measurements we usually use high for things and tall for people.",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "tall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is 6 feet ………………………………",
            "description": "In measurements we usually use high for things and tall for people.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "high",
                "long"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The shelves were too ……………………………… for me to reach.",
            "description": "We use tall to talk about distance above ground.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "long",
                "high"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You have got lovely ……………………………… fingers.",
            "description": "We use long for parts of the body.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "long"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you help me ……………………………….. this problem?",
            "description": "Help is followed by object + infinitive with or without to.",
            "answers": [
                "solve",
                "to solve",
                "to solving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………….. somebody coming.",
            "description": "The word hear is not normally used in the progressive form. ",
            "answers": [
                "could hear",
                "was hearing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I could see him ………………………………… the bus.",
            "description": "Only the ing form is used after can see or could see.",
            "answers": [
                "get off",
                "getting off",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………………. disturb me when I am working",
            "description": "The negative form is usually made with had better + not + infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "had better not",
                "hadn't better"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will pay you back when I ……………………………. a job.",
            "description": "When the verb in the main clause is in the future tense, we use simple present tense in the subordinate clause to refer to future. ",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "got",
                "will get"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}